Department of Mathematics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committees - Faculty of Science, 1965 - 1971; F-14-3; 5 cm of textual records
  - Committee of Science Heads, 1965 - 1969; F-14-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - Science workshop committee, 1966 - 1967; F-14-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - High school liaison committee, 1968 - 1969; F-14-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - Ad hoc Faculty of Science committees, 1967 - 1968; F-14-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - Dean's search committee, 1970 - 1971; F-14-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
- Committees - university, 1965 - 1977; F-14-4; 25 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to University committees on which the Chair or other Department faculty members sat. It includes correspondence, reports and minutes.
  Access to records in the subseries "Appointment of Psychology Head" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Academic services committee, 1966 - 1968; F-14-4-1; 1 cm of textual records
    - Academic Services Commitee, 1966 - 1968; F-14-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - Committee on data processing, 1965 - 1969; F-14-4-2; 3 cm of textual records
    - Committee on data processing, 1965 - 1967; F-14-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - Ad hoc committee to form university committee, President's committee on computing facilities, Computing Science search committee, 1965 - 1967; F-14-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - University committee on data processing, 1967 - 1969; F-14-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
  - Computing science steering committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3; 6 cm of textual records
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-24)
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Computing Science Steering Committee, 1972 - 1977; F-14-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
  - Interdisciplinary committee on university relations, 1967 - 1968; F-14-4-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Interdisciplinary Committee on University Relations, 1967 - 1968; F-14-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
  - President's advisory committee, 1967 - 1968; F-14-4-5; 1 cm of textual records
    - President's Advisory Committee, 1967 - 1968; F-14-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
  - Appointment of Psychology head, 1966 - 1967; F-14-4-6; 5 cm of textual records
    - University Committee on Appointment of psychology head #1, 1966; F-14-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-69)
    - University Committee on Appointment of psychology head #2, 1966 - 1967; F-14-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-69)
  - Scholarships, awards and bursaries, 1975 - 1977; F-14-4-7; 8 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries #1, 1976 - 1977; F-14-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-69)
    - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries #2, 1975 - 1976; F-14-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-69)
    - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries #3, 1975 - 1976; F-14-4-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-69)
- Curriculum and programs, 1965 - 1986; F-14-5; 2.18 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to courses and programs offered by the Department.
  Access to records in the subseries "Courses" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Courses, 1965 - 1986; F-14-5-1; 1.77 m of textual records
    - Course outlines, 1970; F-14-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-25)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1974; F-14-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1974; F-14-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, 1974; F-14-5-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1974; F-14-5-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1974; F-14-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1975; F-14-5-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1975; F-14-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-26)
    - Course reaction surveys, 1975; F-14-5-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1975; F-14-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1975; F-14-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 14-27)
    - Course reaction surveys, #3, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 14-28)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #3, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 14-29)
    - Course reaction surveys, #3, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Course reaction surveys, #3, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Course reaction surveys, #1, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Course reaction surveys, #2, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Mathematics lab summaries, 1977 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Statistics lab summaries, 1977 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - final examination, 1971 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - final examination, 1981 - 1983; F-14-5-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 14-30)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - midterm examination, 1972 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - midterm examination, 1975 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - midterm examination, 1981 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 100 - Survey of college mathematics - final examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1965 - 1969; F-14-5-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1966 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1970 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1975 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 14-31)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - final examination, 1965 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 101 - Introduction to statistics - final examination, 1975 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 101-3 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1974 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 101-3 - Introduction to statistics - midterm examination, 1980 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 101-3 - Introduction to statistics - final examination, 1976 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 101-3 - Introduction to statistics - final examination, 1981 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 104 - midterm examination, 1977 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 104 - final examination, 1977 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 106 - midterm examination, 1969; F-14-5-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 141 - midterm examination, 1974 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 14-32)
    - Math 141 - final examination, 1978 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 142 - midterm examination, 1973 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 142 - final examination, 1973 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 150 - midterm examination, 1971 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 150 - final examination, 1971 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 151 Calculus I - midterm examination, 1969 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 151 Calculus I - midterm examination, 1969 - 1982; F-14-5-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 151 Calculus I - final examination, 1970 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 151 Calculus I - final examination, 1972 - 1975; F-14-5-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 14-33)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - midterm examination, 1975 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - final examination, 1971 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-80 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - midterm examination, 1969 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-81 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - midterm examination, 1977 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-82 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - final examination, 1969 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-83 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 152 Calculus II - final examination, 1978 - 1983; F-14-5-1-0-84 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 154 - midterm examination, 1976 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-85 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 154 - final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-86 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 155 - midterm examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-87 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 155 - final examination, 1977 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-88 (Archival box - standard 14-34)
    - Math 157-3 Calculus for social sciences - midterm examination, 1978 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-89 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 157 Calculus for social sciences - midterm examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-90 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 157-3 Calculus for social sciences - final examination, 1977 - 1983; F-14-5-1-0-91 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 157 Calculus for social sciences - final examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-92 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 158 - midterm examination, 1979 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-93 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 158 - final examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-94 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 161 Statistics - midterm examination, 1970 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-95 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 161 Statistics - final examination, 1970 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-96 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 180 History of Mathematics - midterm examination, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-97 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 180 History of Mathematics - midterm examination, 1973 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-98 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 190 - midterm examination, 1976 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-99 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 190 - final examination, 1977 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-100 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 191 - midterm and final examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-101 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 194 - midterm examination, 1976 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-102 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 194 - final examination, 1975 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-103 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 195 - midterm examination, 1973 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-104 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 195 - final examination, 1972 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-105 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 196 - midterm examination, 1976 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-106 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 196 - final examination, 1977; F-14-5-1-0-107 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 216 - midterm and final examination, 1981; F-14-5-1-0-108 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 232-2 - Elementary linear algebra - midterm examination, 1965 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-109 (Archival box - standard 14-35)
    - Math 232-2 - Elementary linear algebra - midterm examination, 1978 - 1983; F-14-5-1-0-110 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 232-2 - Elementary linear algebra - final examination, 1965 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-111 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 232-2 - Elementary linear algebra - final examination, 1978 - 1984; F-14-5-1-0-112 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 401 - midterm examination, 1975 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-113 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 401 - final examination, 1975 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-114 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 402 - midterm examination, 1974 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-115 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 402 - final examination, 1974 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-116 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 405 - midterm examination, 1970 - 1973; F-14-5-1-0-117 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 405 - final examination, 1970 - 1973; F-14-5-1-0-118 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 406 - midterm examination, 1973; F-14-5-1-0-119 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 406 - final examination, 1970 - 1973; F-14-5-1-0-120 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 408 - midterm examination, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-121 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 408 - final examination, 1979 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-122 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 411 - midterm examination, 1970 - 1972; F-14-5-1-0-123 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 411 - final examination, 1967 - 1972; F-14-5-1-0-124 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 412 - midterm examination, 1969 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-125 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 412 - final examination, 1969 - 1975; F-14-5-1-0-126 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 413 - midterm examination, 1968 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-127 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 413 - final examination, 1968 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-128 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 414 - midterm examination, 1968 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-129 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 414 - final examination, 1968 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-130 (Archival box - standard 14-36)
    - Math 415 - midterm and final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-131 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 416 - midterm examination, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-132 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 416 - final examination, 1974 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-133 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 418 - midterm and final examination, 1981; F-14-5-1-0-134 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 419 - final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-135 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 420 - midterm examination, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-136 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 420 - final examination, 1978 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-137 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 421 - midterm examination, 1967 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-138 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 421 - midterm examination, 1968 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-139 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 422 - final examination, 1971 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-140 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 423 - midterm examination, 1967 - 1968; F-14-5-1-0-141 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 423 - final examination, 1967 - 1972; F-14-5-1-0-142 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 424 - midterm examination, 1967; F-14-5-1-0-143 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 424 - final examination, 1968 - 1969; F-14-5-1-0-144 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 425 - final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-145 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 426, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-146 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 431 - midterm examination, 1973 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-147 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 431 - final examination, 1966 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-148 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 432 - midterm examination, 1967 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-149 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 432 - final examination, 1967 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-150 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 433 - final examination, 1972 - 1975; F-14-5-1-0-151 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 438 - midterm examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-152 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 438 - final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-153 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 439 - final examination, 1980 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-154 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 441 - midterm examination, 1971 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-155 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 441 - final examination, 1967 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-156 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 442 - midterm examination, 1968 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-157 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 442 - final examination, 1967 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-158 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 443 - midterm examination, 1975 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-159 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 443 - final examination, 1976 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-160 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 443 - final examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-161 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 451 - midterm examination, 1967 - 1975; F-14-5-1-0-162 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 451 - final examination, 1969 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-163 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 466 - midterm examination, 1968 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-164 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 466 - final examination, 1968 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-165 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 467 - midterm examination, 1969 - 1975; F-14-5-1-0-166 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 467 - final examination, 1969 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-167 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 468 - midterm examination, 1971 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-168 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 468 - final examination, 1971 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-169 (Archival box - standard 14-37)
    - Math 469 - midterm examination, 1980; F-14-5-1-0-170 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 469 - final examination, 1973 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-171 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 470 - midterm examination, 1972 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-172 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 470 - final examination, 1972 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-173 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 471 - midterm examination, 1972 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-174 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 471 - final examination, 1972 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-175 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 472 - final examination, 1981; F-14-5-1-0-176 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 480 - midterm examination, 1978; F-14-5-1-0-177 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 480 - final examination, 1978 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-178 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 486 - midterm examination, 1974 - 1979; F-14-5-1-0-179 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 486 - final examination, 1972 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-180 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 489 - midterm examination, 1970 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-181 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 489 - final examination, 1970 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-182 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 490 - midterm examination, 1970 - 1976; F-14-5-1-0-183 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 490 - final examination, 1972 - 1980; F-14-5-1-0-184 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 492 - midterm examination, 1972; F-14-5-1-0-185 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 492 - final examination, 1972 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-186 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 493 - final examination, 1976; F-14-5-1-0-187 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 494 - final examination, 1972 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-188 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 495 - midterm examination, 1972 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-189 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 495 - final examination, 1973 - 1977; F-14-5-1-0-190 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 496 - midterm examination, 1972 - 1974; F-14-5-1-0-191 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 496 - final examination, 1972 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-192 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 813 - final examination, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-193 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 820 - final examination, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-194 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 831 - final examination, 1979; F-14-5-1-0-195 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Math 889 - midterm and final examination, 1981; F-14-5-1-0-196 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Textbook lists 100 to 800, 1965 - 1972; F-14-5-1-0-197 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Textbook lists 100 to 200, 1965 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-198 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Textbook lists 300 to 400, 1966 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-199 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Textbook lists - graduate, 1967 - 1978; F-14-5-1-0-200 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Textbook lists - undergraduate, 1976 - 1981; F-14-5-1-0-201 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Undergraduate courses - enrollment patterns, 1965 - 1986; F-14-5-1-0-202 (Archival box - standard 14-38)
    - Undergraduate courses - enrollment patterns, 1965 - 1986; F-14-5-1-0-203 (Archival box - standard 14-38)